A Guide to the Richmond First Club Archives 1919-
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
Richmond First Club Archives 1919-
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
M 238
11.75 linear feet
Richmond First Club
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for use without restrictions
Acquisition Information
Collection donated to the department by the Richmond First Club.
Biographical/Historical Information
Organized in 1919, the Richmond First Club was founded by Dr. Dice R. Anderson and B. Roy Dudley, Jr. to continue the work begun by the Richmond Civic Association. Strictly non-partisan, closed to employees and officials of the city the RFC engages in objective studies of the city's government and offers suggestions for improvements. A more specific history can be found in "A Seventy-Five Year Participation in Local Government: Richmond-First Club 1919-1994" by John H. Whaley.
The Presidents of the Club have been: (* denotes deceased) Jesse F. Wood 1919-1920* Stuart Ragland 1920-1921* B. Roy Dudley, Jr. 1921-1922* Wilmer L. O'Flaherty 1922-1923* Morton L. Wallerstien 1923-1924* J. Vaughan Gary* and Robert A. Brock, Jr.* 1924-1925 Kenneth C. Wood 1925-1926* Irving May 1926-1927* John F. O'Grady,Jr. 1927-1928* B. Roy Dudley, Jr. 1928-1929* E.L. Williams 1929-1930* Ernest H. Perkins 1930-1931 Henry S. Raab 1931-1932* L.C. Bird 1932-1933* F. Milton Garey 1933-1934* J.T. Parkinson, Jr.1934-1935* Dr. R.B. Pinchbeck 1935-1936* R. Hugh Rudd 1936-1937* W. Stirling King 1937-1938 Irving G. Craig* and Dr. Sidney Trattner* 1938-1939 J. Stuart White 1939-1940 William M. Blackwell 1940-1941 Walter Bishop 1941-1942* Hamilton R. Sutton 1942-1943 John K. Peeples, Jr. 1943-1944* John C. MacKinnon 1944-1945 Henry T. Huband 1945-1946* R.W. Winfree, Jr. 1946-1947 Edward S. Hirschler 1947-1948 Allen W. Moore and Clifton B. Cosby 1948-1949 Edwin J. Crockin 1949-1950 Roger D. Johnson 1950-1051* Thomas C. Yeaman 1951-1952 J. Edwin DuPriest 1952-1953 Leroy E. Marlowe 1953-1954* Guy T. Mattox 1954-1955* Hugh R. Thompson, Jr. 1955-1956* R. Pierce Lumpkin 1956-1957 Edward E. Lane 1957-1958 R. Hugh Rudd, Jr. 1958-1959* Ben R. Johns, Jr. 1959- 1960 Robert P. Buford, Jr. 1960-1961 Irving I. Held, Jr. 1961-1962 E. Ballard Baker 1962-1963 Harry Frazier, III 1963-1964 Edward R. Parker 1964-1965 John F. Kay, Jr. 1965-1966 Walker Florance 1966-1967 Arthur C. Beck, Jr. 1967-1968 Thomas N. Parker 1968-1969 Collins Denny III 1969-1970 C. Ray Doggett 1970-1971 Hugh V. White, Jr. 1971-1972 E. Parker Brown 1972-1973 James L. Doherty 1973-1974 William H. Bingham 1974-1975 Charles S. Ylonen 1975-1976 Francis B. Garey 1976-1977 Maxwell G. Cisne 1977-1978 James B. Edge, Jr. 1978-1979 Harry L. Frazier, Jr. 1979-1980 E. Hatcher Crenshaw, Jr. 1980-1981 Gerald P. McCarthy 1981-1982 Hamill D. Jones, Jr. 1982-1983 Kenneth E. Powell 1983-1984 Susan V. Fore Brown 1984-1985 Robert W. Schaberg 1985-1986 George R. Peterson 1986-1987 Robert R. Laha, Jr. 1987-1988 Wayland W. Rennie 1988-1989 Susan S. Peterson 1989-1990 Patrick M. McSweeney 1990-1991 Nikki Nicholau 1991-1992,1992-1993,1993-1994 S. Brian Farmer 1944-1995 Peggy Baggett 1995-1996
Scope and Content Information
The Richmond First Club Papers consist of administrative files, correspondence, reports, memoranda, committee files, publications, audio tapes, photographs and clippings about the Club's activities or interests. The materials encompass the years 1919-1990, but are concentrated in the period from the mid 1970s through the present. Series VIII contains photocopied material from the Raymond Pinchbeck Papers at the Virginia Baptist Historical Society. The bulk of these materials are dated from the 1950s.
Arrangement
Arrangement
The majority of the files are arranged alphabetically and then chronologically. Bulletins are arranged by date. Duplicates have been weeded from the collection and either returned to the Richmond First Club or disposed of. Photographs, video tapes and audio cassette tapes have been transferred to RG 60, 70 and M 15 respectively. The oversized materials are maps of the Richmond area of the 1980s.
Organization
Series I--Administrative Files (n.d., 1928- ); Series II--Committee Files (n.d., 1958- ); Series III--Committee Reports (1969 - ); Series IV--Bulletin (n.d., 1942- ); Series V--Clippings and Miscellaneous Files (n.d., 1963- ); Series VI--Oversize (Located in Map Drawer 26, 1980s); Series VII--RFC 1994 75th Anniversary History; Series VIII--Raymond Pinchbeck Collection of RFC materials (1948-1967)
Contents List
- Series I--Administrative Files, n.d. 1928-1992
  - Administrative Manual, n.d. (Box-folder 1.1)
  - Annual Report 1961-1962 (Box-folder 1.2)
  - Board 1977-1979 (Box-folder 1.3)
  - Board 1978 (Box-folder 1.4)
  - Board 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1.5)
  - Board 1979 (Box-folder 1.6)
  - Board 1985-1986 (Box-folder 2.1)
  - Board 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2.2)
  - Board Meeting Handouts 1987-1989 (Box-folder 2.3)
  - Board Minutes and Annual Reports-Fuhrmann 1965-1967 (Box-folder 2.4)
  - Board Minutes and Annual Reports--Fuhrmann 1968-1969, 1972 (Box-folder 2.5)
  - Board Minutes 1977-1981, 3 folders (Box-folder 2.6-2.8)
  - Board Minutes and Annual Reports 1984-1985 (Box-folder 3.1)
  - Board Minutes and Annual Reports 1986-1987 (Box-folder 3.2)
  - Board Minutes 1988-1991, 4 folders (Box-folder 3.3-3.6)
  - Board Minutes 1992-1996, 4 folders (Box-folder 3-A.1-3-A.4)
  - Budget 1968-1970 (Box-folder 3-A.5)
  - Budget-General Fund Budget, City of Richmond 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3-A.6)
  - Budget 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4.1)
  - Buford, Robert P. 1978-1981, 1983, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box-folder 4.1(1))
  - Certificates of Recognition 1977, 1979 (Box-folder 4.2)
  - Charter Changes-Fuhrmann 1965-1966 (Box-folder 4.3)
  - Committee Reports (Box-folder 4.3(1))
  - Committee on Regional Provision of Services Report, December 1994 (Box-folder 4.3(2))
  - Committee, n.d. 1960, 1978-1985, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 4.4)
  - Constitution and By-laws (Box-folder 4.5)
  - Constitution, President List, Membership Lists-Fuhrmann 1966, 1968 (Box-folder 4.6)
  - Corporate Papers re: Income and Determination of Tax Exempt Status, n.d. 1982 (Box-folder 4.6(1))
  - Correspondence (Box-folder 4.8)
  - Correspondence 1928 (Box-folder 4.9)
  - Correspondence-Fuhrmann 1922-1987, 3 folders (Box-folder 4.10-4.12)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2) 1977-1978 (Box-folder 4.13)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2) 1977-1978 (Box 5.1)
  - Correspondence, n.d. 1976-1977, 1979-1980, 1986, 1990 (Box-folder 5.1(1))
  - Correspondence re: Income and Determination of Tax Exempt Status 1981-1983 (Box-folder 5.1(2))
  - Federal Aid (Box-folder 5.2)
  - First Vice President 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5.3)
  - Good Government Award 1960-1980, 8 folders (Box-folder 5.4-5.10)
  - Good Government Award 1981-1987, 7 folders (Box-folder 6.1-6.7)
  - Good Government Award 1988-1992, 4 folders (Box-folder 7.1-7.4)
  - Good Government Award: Correspondence 1960-1985 (Box-folder 7.5)
  - Good Government Award Correspondence 1977-1979 (Box-folder 7.6)
  - Handbook 1959, 1968, 1971, 1974, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 7.7)
  - Handbook Typescript 1979-1980 (Box-folder 7.8)
  - History (Box-folder 7.4)
  - Luncheons 1989-1990 (Box-folder 7A.1)
  - Meeting (Box-folder 7A.2)
  - Members 1987-1988 (Box-folder 7A.3)
  - Membership (Correspondence) 1948-1991 (Box-folder 7A.4)
  - Membership Directories 1984-1988, 4 folders (Box-folder 7A.5-7A.8)
  - Membership Directory 1988-1989 (Box-folder 8.5)
  - Membership Directory Draft 1985-1986 (Box-folder 8.6)
  - Membership Lists, Mailing Labels--Cain 1985-1987 (Box-folder 8.7)
  - Membership Survey, n.d. (Box-folder 8.7(1))
  - Memoranda, Minutes, Reports-Doherty (Box-folder 8.8)
  - Misc. Memos, Brochures, Correspondence-Cain 1986-1988 (Box-folder 8.9)
  - National Conference for Religious Freedom 1986 (Box-folder 8.9(1))
  - New Members File-Cain 1987 (Box-folder 8.10)
  - Operating Manual; Master Copy/First Draft (Box-folder 8.11)
  - Past Presidents Luncheon 1977 (Box-folder 8.12)
  - Photos from Bulletin 1986-1987 (Box-folder 8.13)
  - Planning File 1977-1978, 3 folders (Box-folder 9.1-9.3)
  - President-Fuhrmann 1965-1966 (Box-folder 9.4)
  - President's File-Fuhrmann 1965-1966 (Box-folder 9.5)
  - Proposed name Change-Doherty 1973-1974 (Box-folder 9.6)
  - Remarks by Gerald P. McCarthy (Box-folder 9.7)
  - Second Vice President 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.1)
  - Secretary 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.2)
  - Secretary's File-Fuhrmann 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box-folder 10.3-10.4)
  - Secretary's File-Begun 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box-folder 10.5-10.6)
  - Secretary's File-Cain 1987 (Box-folder 10.7)
  - Treasurer 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box-folder 10.8-10.9)
- Series II--Committees, n.d. 1958-
  - Child Care (Box -10.9)
  - Convention and Visitor Bureau Advisory (Box-folder 10.10)
  - Develop Recommendations to Grayson Commission (Box-folder 10.11)
  - Economic Power/Development, Working Papers (Box-folder 10.12)
  - Economic Power/Development, Working Papers (Box-folder 11.2)
  - Government Structures 1985 (Box-folder 11.3)
  - Government Structures--Appropriate Size...for...City Council Report 1984 (Box-folder 11.3(1))
  - Governmental Structures-Clippings, n.d. 1964, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box-folder 11.3(2))
  - Governmental Structures--Correspondence, n.d. 1977, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 11.3(3))
  - Governmental Structures--Reports, Articles, Seminars, n.d. 1972, 1975, 1977, 1986 (Box-folder 11.3(4))
  - James River (Box-folder 11.4)
  - James River Roundtable, Planning File (Box-folder 11.5)
  - James River Roundtable, Working Papers (Box-folder 11.6)
  - James River, Working Papers (Box-folder 11.7)
  - James River, Working Papers (Box-folder 11.8)
  - Jurisdictional Cooperation 1985-1987 (Box-folder 12.1-12.2)
  - Jurisdictional Cooperation-Cleveland, Jacksonville, Chicago 1985-1986 (Box-folder 12.3)
  - Jurisdictional Cooperation--Indianapolis 1985-1986 (Box-folder 12.4)
  - Land Use, Working Papers, 2 folders (Box-folder 12.5-12.6)
  - Neighborhood Uplift Seminar 1979, 1981 (Box-folder 13.2(1))
  - Regional Cooperation Structure Committee 1989 (Box-folder 13.2(2))
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Chesterfield, 4 folders (Box-folder 13.3-13.6)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Goochland (Box-folder 13.7)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Goochland (Box-folder 14.1)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Hanover, 2 folders (Box-folder 14.2-14.3)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Henrico (Box-folder 14.4)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Richmond (Box-folder 14.5)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure--Richmond (Box-folder 15.1)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Virginia (Box-folder 15.2)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure-Transportation (Box-folder 15.3)
  - Regional Planning/Cooperation Structure, Working Papers (Box-folder 15.4)
  - Regional Water Authority--Correspondence, Report 1989-1991 (Box-folder 15.5)
  - Taxes and Services 1980-1984 (Box-folder 15.6)
  - Taxes and Services, Correspondence (Box-folder 15.7)
  - Trafficways--Fuhrman 1958, 1960, 1967 (Box-folder 15.8)
  - Urban Renewal-Fuhrman 1958, 1960 (Box-folder 16.1)
- Series III-Committee Reports, n.d. 1969-
  - Air Pollution Control-Fuhrman 1969 (Box-folder 16.2)
  - Analysis of Costs Related to Service Delivery 1989 (Box-folder 16.3)
  - Annexation Laws--Fuhrman (Box-folder 16.4)
  - Appropriate Size and Method of Selection for the Chesterfield County Board of Supervisors--Fuhrman 1983-1984 (Box-folder 16.5-16.6)
  - Areas of Law Affecting Artists (Box-folder 16.7)
  - Causes of Non-Voting in Municipal Elections-Fuhrman 1955 (Box-folder 16.8)
  - Charter Changes 1963 (Box-folder 16.9)
  - Committee Reports 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16.10)
  - Comparison of Taxes and Services (Box-folder 16.11)
  - Comparison of Taxes and Services 1986 (Box-folder 17.1)
  - Economic Power/Development-Cain 1988 (Box-folder 17.2)
  - Economic-Fuhrman, n.d. (Box-folder 17.3)
  - Existing Regional Plans 1989 (Box-folder 17.4)
  - Future of the Capital Area Study Report 1988 (Box-folder 17.4(1))
  - Government Structures in Richmond Metropolitan Area 1986 (Box-folder 17.5)
  - Housing and Urban Renewal-Fuhrman 1966, 1969 (Box-folder 17.6)
  - Housing Study-Cain 1988 (Box-folder 17.7)
  - James River Round Table-Fuhrman 1986 (Box-folder 17.8)
  - Jurisdictional Cooperation 1985-1986 (Box-folder 17.9)
  - Land Use Plans 1987 (Box-folder 17.10)
  - Land Use Plans, Typescript (Box-folder 17.11)
  - Long Range Planning-Fuhrman 1986 (Box-folder 17.12)
  - Mathematics and Science Center 1989 (Box-folder 17.13)
  - Metropolitan Cooperation 1982 (Box-folder 18.1)
  - Metropolitan Cooperation, Typescript (Box-folder 18.2)
  - Metropolitan Police Cooperation-Fuhrman 1968- (Box-folder 18.3)
  - Metropolitan Richmond's James River Corridor 1984 (Box-folder 18.4)
  - Municipal Finance-Fuhrman 1965 (Box-folder 18.5)
  - Planning and Organization-Fuhrman 1965 (Box-folder 18.6)
  - Preliminary Committee Reports 1988, 1992, 2 folders (Box-folder 18.7-18.8)
  - Project on Increasing Intraregional Cooperation with the Richmond Metropolitan Area 1989 (Box-folder 18.9)
  - Regional Plan Survey 1989 (Box-folder 18.10)
  - Regional Planning and Cooperation-Fuhrman, n.d. (Box-folder 18.11)
  - Restoration of Richmond's Canal System--Cain 1988 (Box-folder 18.12)
  - Review of Three Cities 1986 (Box-folder 18.13)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Commission 1987 (Box-folder 19.1)
  - Schools-Fuhrman 1956-1962 (Box-folder 19.2)
  - Taxes and Services 1985-1986 (Box-folder 19.3)
  - Technical and Vocational Education-Fuhrman 1964 (Box-folder 19.4)
  - Trafficways 1967 (Box-folder 19.5)
  - Transportation Study 1988 (Box-folder 19.6)
  - United Health Fund, Report and Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 19.7)
  - VCU-Fuhrman, n.d. (Box-folder 19.8)
  - Voter's Rights-Fuhrman 1972 (Box-folder 19.9)
  - Ward Representation-Fuhrman, n.d. (Box-folder 19.10)
  - Welfare-Fuhrman 1974 (Box-folder 19.11)
- Series IV--Bulletin, n.d. 1942-
  - Bulletin Editor 1977-1978 (Box-folder 19.12)
  - Bulletin, General Information (Box-folder 19.13)
  - Bulletin 1942-1946 (Box-folder 19.14)
  - Bulletin 1947-1984, 6 folders (Box-folder 20.1-20.6)
  - Bulletin 1985-1996 (Box-folder 21.1-21.5)
- Clippings and Miscellaneous Files, n.d. 1963-
  - Appreciation of City Council Resolution-Doherty 1975 (Box-folder 21.4)
  - Change in City Elections: Voting Rights Act--Doherty 1972-1975 (Box-folder 21.5)
  - Clippings 1967-1988 (Box-folder 21.6)
  - Citizens Committee to Commemorate the Virginia Statute of Religious Freedom 1985 (Box-folder 21.7)
  - City Council-Fuhrman 1963 (Box-folder 21.8)
  - Critical Commentary from an Interested Party, n.d. (Box-folder 22.1)
  - Dissolution of City Charter-Doherty 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22.2)
  - Economic Growth as a Function of Local Government Policy-Fuhrman 1975 (Box-folder 22.3)
  - Electing Mayors and Council Members at Large 1969, 1984, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 22.3(1))
  - Emergency Shelter, Inc. (Box-folder 22.4)
  - Future of the Capital Area v. 1 and 2 (Box-folder 22.5)
  - Governor's Commission: Urban Development Policy-Doherty 1974 (Box-folder 22.6)
  - Governor's Commission: Urban Development 1975-1980, 2 folders (Box-folder 22.6(1-2))
  - Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future-Doherty (Box-folder 22.7)
  - Henrico County Annual Report-Fuhrman (Box-folder 22.8)
  - Human Needs in Housing 1964 (Box-folder 22.9)
  - James River as Common Wealth 1984 (Box-folder 22.10)
  - Major Streets and Highways, City of Richmond-Fuhrman 1957 (Box-folder 22.11)
  - Marshaling Citizen Power to Modernize Corrections 1972 (Box-folder 22.12)
  - Mayoral Blue Ribbon Commission 1986 (Box-folder 22.13)
  - McKinsey Proposals-Doherty 1974 (Box-folder 22.14)
  - National Conference on Managed Gowth-Doherty (Box-folder 22.15)
  - Need to Review Virginia's Local Government Structure 1988 (Box-folder 22.16)
  - Open Education-Doherty 1972 (Box-folder 22.17)
  - Plan of Government for the Richmond Region 1959 (Box-folder 22.18)
  - Plan of Government for the Richmond Region 1959 (Box-folder 22.18)
  - Public Utilities-Fuhrman 1963 (Box-folder 22.19)
  - Regional Solid Waste Management Plan Draft 1984 (Box-folder 22.20)
  - Resolution: Port Authority-Fuhrman (Box-folder 23.1)
  - Retail Trade Activity 1977-1982 (Box-folder 23.2)
  - Richmond Chamber of Commerce 1977-1978 (Box-folder 23.3)
  - Richmond Community Action Program 1986-1987 (Box-folder 23.4)
  - Richmond Dog Control Statistics 1970 (Box-folder 23.5)
  - Richmond Harbor Facts 1970 (Box-folder 23.6)
  - Richmond Magazine Article (Box-folder 23.7)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Area Archeological Survey v.1 (Box-folder 23.8)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Area Archeological Survey v.2 (Box-folder 23.9)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority-Fuhrman 1968 (Box-folder 24.1)
  - Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority (Box-folder 24.2)
  - Richmond/Tri-Cities Area Resource Recovery Economic Feasibility Study 1988 (Box-folder 24.3)
  - School Board, Desegregation, Urban Planning, etc. (Box-folder 24.3(1))
  - School Board, Integration, Concerned Citizens, etc. #2-5, 4 folders (Box-folder 24.3(2-5))
  - Route 288 (Box-folder 24.4)
  - Ward System-Doherty (Box-folder 24.5)
- Series VI--Oversize
  - Oversize Folder 1, overized (Map-case 26.1)
    Includes Three editions of Hanover Living Guide and a Copy of the Richmond Business Journal December 1986. Also included are maps of Chesterfield County, Goochland County and Henrico County.
- Series VII--RFC 75th Anniversary History
  - Draft of A Seventy-Five Participation in Local Government RFC history by John Whaley, Jr. 1919-1994 (Box-folder 25.1)
  - History Committee 1989-1990 (Box-folder 25.2)
  - Transcript of interview with Susan Brown (Box-folder 25.3)
  - Transcript of interview with Robert Buford (Box-folder 25.4)
  - Transcript of interview with Jim Doherty (Box-folder 25.5)
  - Transcript of interview with Irving Held (Box-folder 25.6)
  - Transcript of interview with Ed Hirschler (Box-folder 25.7)
  - Transcript of interview with Ed Lane (Box-folder 25.8)
  - Transcript of interview with Jerry McCarthy (Box-folder 25.9)
  - Transcript of interview with Pat McSweeney (Box-folder 25.10)
  - Transcript of interview with George Peterson (Box-folder 25.11)
  - Transcript of interview with Stuart White (Box-folder 25.12)
  - Transcript of interview with Tom Yeaman (Box-folder 25.13)
- Series VIII--Raymond Pinchbeck Collection of RFC Materials 1948-1967
  - Annual Reports 1955-1957, 2 folders (Box-folder 26.1-26.2)
  - Attendance 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26.2(1))
  - Bulletins 1957 (Box-folder 26.3)
  - Bulletins and Correspondence 1957-1958 (Box-folder 26.4)
  - Bulletins 1958-1960 (Box-folder 26.5)
  - Bulletins, reports 1959, 3 folders (Box-folder 26.6-26.8)
  - Bulletins, reports 1959-1960, 1963, 2 folders (Box-folder 26.9-26.10)
  - Bulletins 1964-1967, 4 folders (Box-folder 26.11-26.14)
  - Correspondence 1955-1957, 1960, 3 folders (Box-folder 27.1-27.3)
  - Good Government Award Nominations 1955, 2 folders (Box-folder 27.4-27.5)
  - Good Government Award Letters of Invitation to Special Guests 1956 (Box-folder 27.6)
  - Good Government Award 1956-1959, 4 folders (Box-folder 27.7-27.10)
  - Good Government Award Reservations (Box-folder 27.11)
  - Minutes 1954-1958, 8 folders (Box-folder 28.1-28.8)
  - Miscellaneous 1954-1961, 5 folders (Box-folder 29.1-29.4(1))
  - Miscellaneous Reports 1948, 1955-1957, 3 folders (Box-folder 29.5-29.7)
  - Miscellaneous Committees and Reports 1959-1960 (Box-folder 30.1)
  - News Clippings and Miscellaneous 1956-1958 (Box-folder 30.2)
  - Old Timer's Night 1959 (Box-folder 30.3)
  - Pamphlets 1952-1956 (Box-folder 30.4)
  - Photograph: Sen. Barry Goldwater (Box-folder 30.5)
  - Recent Programs List 1955-1956 (Box-folder 30.6)
  - Administrative manual 1993 (Box-folder 31.1)
  - Associates Committee 1997 (Box-folder 31.2)
  - Attendance 1994-1995 (Box-folder 31.3)
  - Board Meetings Agendas and Notes 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.4)
  - Board-Recommendations to Membership (n.d.) (Box-folder 31.5)
  - Board Meetings/Minutes 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.6)
  - Board Meeting-Minutes 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.7)
  - Board Meeting-Minutes 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31.8)
  - Board Meeting-Misc. 1995-1996 (Box-folder 31.9)
  - Board-Roster 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.10)
  - Brochure 1996 (Box-folder 31.11)
  - Buddy List 1997 (Box-folder 31.12)
  - Budget 1995-1997 (Box-folder 31.13)
  - Bulletins 1996 (Box-folder 31.14)
  - Bulletins 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.15)
  - Bulletins 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31.16)
  - Club Brochures, n.d. (Box-folder 31.17)
  - Club History, n.d. (Box-folder 31.18)
  - Club Meetings Materials 1997 (Box-folder 31.19)
  - Committees General, n.d. (Box-folder 31.20)
  - Committees 1998 (Box-folder 31.21)
  - Committee Topic and Interest Survey 1993 (Box-folder 31.22)
  - Correspondence 1996-1998 (Box-folder 31.23-31.24)
  - Directory, n.d. (Box-folder 31.25)
  - Forms 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.26)
  - Goals/Notes 1997 (Box-folder 31.27)
  - Guest and Potential Member List, n.d. (Box-folder 31.28)
  - Information (Re: Richmond Speakers Handouts) 1997 (Box-folder 31.29)
  - Invoices/Budget 1997 (Box-folder 31.30)
  - Issues and Options, Vol. 1 No. 1, n.d. (Box-folder 31.31)
  - Leadership Talks 1996 (Box-folder 31.32)
  - Leadership 1998 (Box-folder 31.33)
  - League Dinner 1996 (Box-folder 31.34)
  - Letter to Mike Brooks 1997 (Box-folder 31.35)
  - Letters on Past Presidents (Box-folder 31.36)
  - Logo Designs 1993 (Box-folder 31.37)
  - Management Issue 1996 (Box-folder 31.38)
  - Margot Garcia Speakers 1997 (Box-folder 31.39)
  - Marketing 1997 (Box-folder 31.40)
  - Membership Applications, n.d. (Box-folder 31.41)
  - Membership 1997 (Box-folder 31.42)
  - Membership Info, n.d. (Box-folder 31.43)
  - Membership Sign-up and Attendance Lists 1995-1996 (Box-folder 31.44)
  - Membership Sign-In Lists 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.45)
  - Misc. (Minutes, Lists, Letters) 1997 (Box-folder 31.46)
  - Nominating Committee 1997 (Box-folder 31.47)
  - President's Letter 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31.48)
  - Publicity 1994-1996 (Box-folder 31.49)
  - Recruitment 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.50)
  - Registered Agent 1997 (Box-folder 31.51)
  - Revenue Sharing Committee 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box-folder 31.52-31.53)
  - Revenue Sharing Committee-Forum 1997 (Box-folder 31.54)
  - Richmond First Club II 1996 (Box-folder 31.55)
  - Richmond-First, Extra Debate Materials 1995-1996 (Box-folder 32.1)
  - Speakers 1998 (Box-folder 32.2)
  - Treasurer/Balance Sheet 1996-1998 (Box-folder 32.3)
  - 75th Anniversary-Announcements, mailing lists, etc. 1994 (Box-folder 32.4)
  - Richmond First Club Bulletins May 1977-June 1990 (Box 32)
    Includes one undated issue which seems to be from sometime in December, 1979 or January, 1980
  - Richmond First Club Minutes August 1977-November 1987 (Box 32)